Hi, in the segment we're going to be talking about a trick catch called the flamingosis.
Now a flamingosis is very similar to the flamingo.
With the flamingo you’re actually going to be catching it with one leg.
On one leg with the other leg lifted.
This is a flamingo catch.
You also want to keep the leg nice and straight and the toe pointed as much as possible.
Now with a flaming is your going to be spinning the opposite direction rather than spinning into the catch your going to be spinning away from the catch and catching it here.
So in order to do that you need to have the set come right on the outside of your knee.
So when you turn the first view will be right here.
So we're going to try that one now with a self set I am going to have the Frisbee here I am going set it.
Spin around swing your leg over the top of the Frisbee.
That's very important I'm going to try another one.
I am going to set it here spin around and catch it there.
Flamingosis you can do you can add spins before them.
You could do it off of a roll set.
You can do it off of a lot of different sets or even a throw but the flamingosis is a really cool catch.